

COVER LETTER

To whom it may concern.

With 10 years experience in hospitality & customer service industry, I always have felt thrilled to see my clients having good experience on my service as it gives me genuine happiness and satisfaction. But through the long term of the industry, I started realising that the world relies more on web connections rather than face to face connections. Thanks to one of my good friend who is a professional developer, I have been suggested to start studying IT in Coder Academy. It started from my career concern, but now it is a genuine fun and interest in my life.

"Diligent, Patient and Supportive"

My strength is when I have a challenge, I get much patient and diligent. Such as on a project I have worked for, I never had a fear about sitting in front of a desk and thinking deeply to analyse and break down the problem. And when I used to work for a marketing team, I have spared many hours on design and testing. It was not easy moment, but I loved the time I have worked on it. In a team relationship, I am reliable and voluntarily. It is worthy enough as I believe that for a frictionless environment and close-knit team works. I feel achievement and satisfaction in knowing that whoever I worked with feels heartfelt thanks.

"Trustful developer"

In over 800 hours studying of Coder Academy, I have explored and learned HTML, CSS, Python, Flask, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, React and more. This journey gave me confidence that I do want to grow up as a developer. For sure, I still have a lot of more to learn yet, but I believe the practical experience from the real world can make me grown up more.

I know that people who do their best with their team can achieve more than those who try to be the best alone. My goal is here, to be a trustful developer for clients who want to see better future. I hope I can start my step from your team.

Kind regards.
CHANG-HA LEE (Ryan)

RYAN LEE

JUNIOR DEVELOPER



0468 426 279



clidelee@gmail.com



https://github.com/RyanWoolf



www.linkedin.com/in/lionwolfhaus



Fortitude Valley, OLD

ABOUT ME

For the past 10 years, I've been working in the hospitality field. Through that time, I was able to learn good communication skills with team members or with clients. I'm still a junior developer with few experience, but I know I'm a team player and how to work within a team. I'll look forward to have a chat about myself and what I can do for a team.

EDUCATION

Diploma of information technology

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023 Coder Academy, BRISBANE QLD

Diploma of management

Aug 2014 - Jul 2015 Business Institute of Australia, SYDNEY NSW

KEY SKILLS

Professional Skills

HTML, CSS MongoDB
Python Express.js
JavaScript React
PostgreSQL Node.js

Technical Skills

Team communication & work
Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign
Photography
UI / UX Design
Social Media
Wordpress

REFERENCES

References available upon request

WORK EXPERIENCE

Queensland Performing Arts Centre

F&B ATTENDANT

SOUTH BRISBANE QLD | Feb 2022 - Present

• Barista, cocktails & wines, customer service

Motorwagen

HEAD BARISTA & MARKETING TEAM

BRISBANE CITY QLD | Sep 2018 - May 2022

- Web design design and renewal of the webpage
- Graphic design design event posters and vouchers etc
- Contents create photograph, video recording
- Barista, cocktails, customer service

Caffe Cherrybeans

MANAGER

WODEN ACT & BRISBANE AIRPORT | June 2013 – June 2017

- Barista, Customer Service, Training and hiring staff
- Conduct with suppliers, Supplier payment control.

KEY PROJECTS

Restaurant POS system | Nov 2022

Python, Flask

API web-server project on Python and RDBMS(PostgreSQL).

Restaurant tycoon | Oct 2022

Python, Shell

Terminal app based on Python with interacting of user.

Portfolio website | Sep 2022

HTTP CSS

Online portfolio website provides information about myself.

Graphic designs | 2020 - 2021

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

Design event posters, vouchers and renewal of the website .